EUGENE **LEE**

GRADUATE STUDENT

STATEMENT.....

I am a passionate and motivated graduate who has studied in Korea, India and Ireland which has helped give me a broader vision and I believe my experiences in various cultures and various roles will allow me to bring something new to the team.

SKILLS.....

AWS C

Agile Python Serverless Java

Microservices HTML/CSS/JS

Git NodeJS
TDD React
CI/CD PHP

REFERENCES.....

Lejla Rovacanin

Professor | Technology University Dublin

Phone: +353 1 405 2893

Email: Lejla.Rovacanin@TUDublin.ie

Inho Lee

Professor | Geyonggi University

Phone: +82 10 5326 1989 Email: naninho@hanmail.net

Monique Walsh

Owner Director | ELTA School

Phone: +353 86 352 6485 **Email:** hello@elta.ie



7 Wells Drive Dukinfield SK16 5RS United Kingdom



linkedin.com/in/iameugeneleepinkfjgh@gmail.com



+44 75 9399 3129 +82 10 7536 1989



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

RESEARCH ASSISTANT

KOIPA | june 2020-dec 2020

Develop an automate tool to scrape product data to be analysed for violations to intellectual property rights.

ONLINE MODERATOR

Ideal Company | jul 2020-oct 2020

Review content that has been flagged by users or systems and escalated. Investigate and resolve complex issues regarding content.

IT TECHNICIAN INTERN

ELTA School | jun 2018-dec 2018

Design and implement a live chat bot for potential prospective students. Respond to support requests from end users and helped troubleshoot issues.



EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

BACHELOR OF TECHNOLOGY - 1st [80%]

Technology University Dublin, Ireland | 2016-2019

Gain valuable skills in network security, web design and web services. Knowledge and understanding of Networking foundations (LAN, WAN, Wireless, OS, Routing & Switching, IP/TCP/UDP), Web Development (HTML, CSS, JS, PHP) and Software programming languages (C, Java, Python).